(门铃)
(Door bell)
杰森:有人听到吗?我在这工作.有人答应吗?
Jason: Would somebody get that?I'm working here.
好,好!我得挣钱,
Could somebody answer the door?Fine, fine!
我得缴税,我还得开门.生活真充实.
I make the money, I pay the taxes, I'll answer the door.Life is full.
伯尼:你想要开始吗?
Bernie: You want to get started?
杰森:伯尼,你在这干什么?
Jason: Bernie, what are you doing here?
伯尼:你的税.就像每年的这个时候.
Bernie: Your taxes.Like every year at this time.
杰森:哦,你没有得到我的消息?
Jason: Oh, you didn't get my message?
不,今年我不需要会计师,
No I don't need my accountant this year Bernie.
伯尼.我准备自己做缴税的帐.
I'm going to do m y taxes myself.
伯尼:是,我知道了,但是,哈,我不相信你.
Bernie: Yeah, I got it, but, ha, I dint believe you.
杰森:伯尼,我是认真的.今年我自己做缴税的帐.
Jason: Bernie, I'm serious.This year I want to do my own taxes.
伯尼:啊,有个问题.你自己装修这个房间的吗?
Bernie: Ah, one question.Did you decorate this room yourself?
杰森:不,我妻子.
Jason: No, my wife did.
伯尼:是,但是你娶了她.
Bernie: Yeah, but you married her.
杰森:嗨,读我的嘴唇……
Jason: Hey, read my lips..
伯尼:我知道,我知道……没有新税.很好.
Bernie: I know, I know...No new taxes.It's good.
杰森:再见,伯尼.
Jason: Goodbye Bernie.
伯尼:这么来看;你花在我身上的每块钱都是免税的,事实上你省了一块钱.
Bernie: Look at it this way; every dollar you spend on me is deductible,
告诉你,
so you actually save a dollar.
如果双倍收费,你节省的更多.
Tell you what, I'll charge you double, you'll save a fortune.
杰森:出去.
Jason: And stay out.
本:爸爸.现在是我自我介绍的好时候吗?
Ben: Dad.Would now be a good time to introduce myself?
杰森:不.
Jason: No.
本:爸爸,你见了本西维尔儿子,不是本 西维尔企业家.
Ben: Dad, you've met Ben Seaver son, not Ben Seaver entrepreneur.
杰森:本,行了,
Jason: Ben, come on I_m doing my taxes here.I'm in a foul mood.
我在做我的缴税的帐.我心情不好.你真的想坚持你所要坚持的吗?
Do you really want to persist with whatever you are persisting with?
本:我可以给你打电话吗,杰森?
Ben: May I call you Jason?
杰森:不可以,本.
Jason: No Ben.
本:杰森,我想和你谈生意.生意人对生意人.
Ben: Jason, I'd like to talk business.One business man to another.
杰森:那是我的公文包.
Jason: That's my brief case.
本:你妻子好吗?
Ben: How's the Mrs.?
杰森:这就是你关于商业会议的想法,本?
Jason: Is that your idea of a business meeting Ben?
这更多像是你从某本书上看来的.
It sounds more like something you read in a book.
本:我认为现在是讲笑话的好时候.
Ben: I think now would be a good time for a good dirty joke.
杰森:我想干什么,本?
Jason: What are you after Ben?
本:爸爸,你是否经常对自己说"我为什么没有自己的事业?"
Ben: Dad, how often have you said to yourself "Why can't I have my own
"为什么我自己不当老板?""为什么……"
career?" Why can't I be my own boss?" Why ...
杰森:我打断你一下,本.
Jason: Let me interrupt you here Ben.I do have my own career.
我有自己的事业.我是自己的老板.
I am my own boss.
本:你是?
Ben: You are?
杰森:我是精神病医生.
Jason: I'm a psychiatrist.
本:是吗?
Ben: Yeah?
杰森:本,你认为我每天在干什么?
Jason: Ben, what do you think I do every day?
本:老实说,我从来没有多想.
Ben: To be honest, I never gave it much thought.
本:但是你从没有听过我的想法.
Ben: But you haven't heard my idea.
杰森:听着,为了你,
Jason: Listen, the US government gives me a two thousand deduction for you,
美国政府给了我两千块的减免,就这些,你白费力气了.
and that's all, and you're pushing it.
本:杰森,你就给我五分钟,
Ben: Jason, just give me five minutes of your time,
如果你还没兴趣,你就永远见不到我.
and if you're still not interested, you'll never see me again.
杰森:永远不?
Jason: Never again?
本:(在电视上)谢谢你,本.
Ben: (on TV) Thank you Ben.
本:别客气,本.
Ben: You're welcome Ben.
本:(在电视上)嗨,那是我名字.
Ben: (on TV) Hey, that's my name.
本:哈哈哈.
Ben: Ha ha ha.
杰森:永远走了,对吗?
Jason: Gone forever, right?
本:(在电视上)我想为你指个经济独立的道路.
Ben: (on TV) I'm about to show you the road to financial independence.
杰森:本,你都录下了克莉丝的出生!
Jason: Ben, you tapes over Chrissy's birth!
本:不.这只是我为学校里的家伙制作的复制品.
Ben: No.This is just a double I made for the guys at school.
嗨,嗨,回来了.
Hey hey, it's coming back.
本:(在电视上)好呀.音乐.
Ben: (on TV) That's right.Music.But why take it from me?
但是为什么听我说呢?听听典型的美国少年.
Here it from typical America teens.
斯丁基:(在电视上)天呀.对我来说,
Stinky: (on TV) Jeepers.The most important thing for me is music.
最重要的就是音乐.
I spend every dime I can on today's popular music groups.
我花了我每一分钱在当今的流行音乐组合上.但是我只是得到一个耳环.
And I just got an ear ring.
劳拉-林恩:(在电视上)哇,哇!但是严肃地,我在想这些热的发烫的乐队哪来的.
Laura-Lynn: (on TV) Wow, wow!But seriously, I am concerned about where the hot new groups are coming from.
开萝尔:(在电视上)我从没想过音乐能够如此的好,直到我亲自见过他们.
Carol: (on TV) I didn't think music could be so good until I saw them
我已经完成了吗?
in person.Am I done yet?
克莉丝:(在电视上)我笑,我哭,我超出年龄的感动.像那?
Chrissy: (on TV) I laughed, I cried, I was moved beyond my years.Like that?
本:(在电视上)那些年轻人谈论些什么呢?新鲜小子!
Ben: (on TV) Just what are all these young people talking about?The Fresh kids!
在电视上的每个人:是呀,哇,啊!
Everyone on TV: Yeah, wow, ahhhh!
开萝尔:(在电视上)我完成了吧?
Carol: (on TV) Am I done yet?
歌曲:我在寻觅像你这样的人.我在寻找,但是我不能忘记你.有人说天空是极限,但是女孩,如果有爱,你知道我在里面.那是我的心,那是我的灵魂,我试图去寻找另一个,但是我不能.难道你不知道你随着街舞飞翔.她的长的光滑的腿使得她永远向前.走在林荫大道上,制造快乐.你是我一直梦见的姑娘.你从头到脚抚摩我,说你爱我,你永远不让我走.你是让我梦想变成现实的那位.这需要很长时间……是呀,哇!
Song: I'm looking for someone like you.I'm searching but I can't get my mind
off you.Some say that the sky is the limit, but girl if there's a
love you know I'm in it.It's in my heart, it's in my soul, I
try to find another but I can't let go.Don't you know you fly with
the hip hop lot?Her long sleek legs keep her going none stop.Walking on
the boulevard, making fun.You're the one that I dream about all the time.You
were caressing me from head to toe, saying that you loved me and you'll never
let me go.You're the one to make my dreams come true.It will take
a long time....Yeah, wow
本:爸爸.
Ben: See dad.I've been helping The Fresh kids set up for parties and stuff
我正在帮新鲜小子准备晚会和素材,
and everybody goes crazy when they see them.
每个人见到他们都跟发疯似的.他们将比街区新小子强大.
They are going to be bigger than New Kids On The Block.
现在他们所需要的就是一个经理.
Now all that they need is a manager.
杰森:谁告诉你你可以使用我的摄象机的?
Jason: Who told you you could use my video camera?
本:爸爸,爸爸,爸爸.
Ben: Dad, dad dad.You are missing the big picture here.
你在丧失美好前景.现在新鲜小子有能力成为巨星.
Now The Fresh kids have the talent to become monsters.
那是音乐界说的.现在,我懂的不多,
That's music business talk.Now I don't know much, ok I don't know anything.
好,我什么都不懂.但是我懂得音乐,
But I do know music and I do know these guys are good.
而且我知道这些小子很棒.而且我还知道,
And I also know that if you don't go for this,
如果你不去,我就游荡余生,就像迈克.
I'm going to end up a bum for the rest of my life, like Mike.
杰森:好,你想从我这得到什么,本?
Jason: Alright, well what do you want from me Ben?
本:爸爸,你不仅仅要成为经理,你还要投资.这就是我为什么让你成为我合伙人的原因.
Ben: Dad, you don't just become a manager, you have to invest.That's why I want you to become my partner.
杰森:哦,我根本不懂得什么管理.
Jason: Oh, I don't know anything about managing.
本:那么,在拉格泰姆音乐杂志上有完整的文章.明白吗?
Ben: Well, there's a whole article about it in Ragtime magazine.See?
他们开豪华轿车,订房间服务.你很适合这工作.
Here, they ride in limos and order room service.You're perfect for the job.
杰森:我想事情还多着呢.
Jason: Well I'm sure there is more to it than that.
本:爸爸,你是个已婚男人.
Ben: Dad, you are a married man.
杰森:不是那个方面.
Jason: Not that.
本:我知道这有很多工作,但是我已经全部想好了.瞧,
Ben: I know it's a lot of work, but I've got it all figured out.
好了.我们拍点宣传照片,
See, ok.We get some publicity pictures and some new wardrobe.
买些行头.制作一张唱片,然后就坐在后面看着钱滚滚而来.
Make a demo, then just sit back and watch the money roll in.
杰森:我从来没有见过你对一个主意如此兴奋,本.
Jason: I've never seen you this excited about an idea Ben.
本:是呀,如果我们不赶快行动,
Ben: Yeah, and if we don't move fast some other manager will sign them up.
其它经理人就会和他们签约.因此,
So tomorrow why don't you come with me?
明天你为什么不和我一道呢?他们将作为摇滚有线电视绣的嘉宾.
They are going to be guests on the cable show "Rack and Roll".
杰森:那么现在你已经考虑好的整个事情?
Jason: So you've figured this whole thing out now?
本:我把告诉你的事情都操练了.包括那个笑话.
Ben: I've practiced what I was going to tell you.Including the dirty joke.
顺便说句,你该听听.
Which by the way you really should hear some time.
杰森:好的,本.底线;大概需要花我多少钱?
Jason: Ok Ben.Bottom line; how much would this cost me?
本:六万三千.
Ben: Sixty three thousand dollars.
杰森:哦,哦哦哦.天哪.
Jason: Oh, ho ho ho.Yeah.
本:不.
Ben: No.
杰森:嗬嗬嗬.
Jason: Ho ho ho.
本:本,那就两千.
Ben: Ok, I'll settle for two thousand.
迈克:真业余.
Mike: Such an amateur.
克莉丝:你怎么得逞的?
Chrissy: How would you have done it?
马克:首先,我选择了凌晨一点到四点.这段时间是爸爸最弱的时候.还有,我略施小计,我告诉爸爸,我需要进行一个手术,医生只收现金.
Mike: Well first, I would have picked one to four am.That's when dad is
usually at his weakest.Right, and the, off the top of my head, I'd probable
tell dad that I needed an operation from a surgeon who only takes cash
开萝尔:那么这就是略施小计呀.
Carol: And to think that is just from the top of his head.
迈克:行了,瞧这,克莉丝.这是我的机会准备饭菜了.爸爸,爸爸.我告诉那个孩子别来烦你.我不明白,他哪来的想法把你当成摇钱树.行了,我把他带出去.我要跟他谈谈.你给我二十块钱买汉堡?
Mike: Alright, watch this Chrissy.This is my chance to get a few table scraps.Dad, dad.I told the boy not to bother you.I don't know where he gets the idea that you are made of money.Alright, I'll take him out.I'll talk to him.You got twenty bucks for a couple of burgers?
杰森:迈克,迈克,没有看到我们在进行重要的商务会谈?
Jason: Mike, Mike, cant you see we are having an important business meeting here.
迈克:是呀,对.
Mike: Yeah right.
本:猜猜谁拿出两千块钱.
Ben: Guess who just coughed up two thousand bucks?
迈克:什么?两千……但是爸爸.
Mike: What?Two thou...But dad.
开萝尔:出去,滑头先生.
Carol: Get out Mr.Smooth.
克莉丝:我们什么时候得到我们的饭菜?
Chrissy: So when do we get our table scraps?
麦琪:亲爱的,我们得谈谈.我刚在本的房间里发现一些另人担心的东西.
Maggie: Honey, we have to talk.I just found something very upsetting in Ben's room
杰森:哦,亲爱的,放松点.每个他这么大的孩子都有这些杂志.
Jason: Oh honey, just relax.Every kid his age has those kind of magazines.
克莉丝:站森,我在说这事.
Chrissy: Jason, I am talking about this.A check for two thousand dollars.
一张两千块钱的支票.他一定伪造了你的签名.
He must have forged your signature.
不仅这样,他甚至说是乱写.
And its not even close, he when for an exaggerated type anal scrawl.
杰森:麦琪,我给他的.
Jason: Maggie, I gave it to him.
麦琪:你什么?
Maggie: You what?
杰森:是,是.本和我现在经营一个新的摇滚乐队.
Jason: Yeah, yeah.Ben and I are now managing a new rock band.
麦琪:经营乐队!
Maggie: Managing a band!
杰森:其实不是什么真的乐队.就是三个孩子上窜下跳.
Jason: Well it's not really a band.It's just three kids jumping up and down.
麦琪:你给他两千块钱?
Maggie: And you gave him two thousand dollars?
杰森:是.
Jason: Yep.
麦琪:哦,可怜的人.
Maggie: Oh, my poor muffin man.
哦,小甜心,我知道不使用会计师是个错误.
Oh sweetheart, I knew it was a mistake not to use an accountant.
杰森:不,这跟税无关,
Jason: No, this is nothing to do with doing taxes Maggie.
麦琪.我没有行为反常.但是我还没有给本两千块钱.
I haven't freaked out.But I haven't given Ben two thousand dollars.
我只是投资我儿子.行了,
I merely invested in our son.Come on, haven't you seen, the kid's changed.
难道你没有看的出来,孩子变了.他穿西服,
He's there in a suit and he's been thinking the whole thing through.
而且把整件事情从头到尾想了一通.他甚至给我讲了笑话.
He even told me a dirty joke.
麦琪:哦,真没想象到.
Maggie: Oh imagine that.
杰森:但是很兴奋,麦琪.
Jason: But the excitement Maggie.He had such enthusiasm.
他有如此的热情.我之前从来没有见过他这样子.他眼睛里有真实的光芒.
I've never seen that look in him before.He had a real spark in his eye.
这样的目光看着我,我没法说不.
I can't say no to somebody who looks at me like that.
麦琪:我需要一辆法拉利.
Maggie: I want a Ferrari.
杰森:那是闪烁;我说的是光芒.
Jason: Well that's a twinkle; I'm talking about a sparkle.
麦琪:好,就坐在那里,以你脸上的表情.
Maggie: Fine, just sit there with that look on your face.
迈克:什么?
Mike: What?
麦琪:表演的就好象这两千块钱的骗局跟你无关.表演的好象那钱不是从你爸爸那里通过本进入你的口袋.
Maggie: Act like you weren't behind this two thousand dollar scam.
Act liker that money isn't going right from your father through Ben into
your pocket.
迈克:妈妈,妈妈.
Mike: Mum, mum.I don't know what you are talking about.I'm serious.
我不知道你在说什么.
I don't have a clue how that little meat ball got two grand out of little
我是认真的.我真的不知道那小子怎么从爸爸那里弄来两千块钱.
muffin man in there.
本:那些钱是用于广告的.现在,
Ben: And that's it for publicity.Now, for the demo.
关于唱片.
If we are willing to record at four am,
如果我们将在早上四点录制,我已经找到只需要五百块钱的地方来录制.
I've found a place that will do it for five hundred dollars.
杰森:哦,本.五百块钱,真贵.
Jason: Oh Ben.Five hundred, that's real expensive.
本:爸爸,我已经查过了电话簿里的每个录音棚.
Ben: Dad I checked every studio in the phone book.
杰森:我也知道一点音乐,本.
Jason: Well I know a little bit about music Ben.
我在大学里也录制了一两张唱片.
I cut a demo or two in college you know.
本:爸爸,我们在这里讨论音乐,
Ben: Dad, we are talking about music here,
而不是一群老家伙上窜下跳.
not a bunch of old guys jumping up and down.
杰森:我不错的,本.
Jason: I was good Ben.
很多人认为我是下一个加里 帕克特.
A lot of people thought I would be the next Gary Pucket.
我有告诉过你我真正见到家里 帕克特?
Did I ever tell you about the time I actually met Gary Pucket?
你知道他跟我说什么了吗?他……
You know what he said to me?He...
本:说你有他见过的白人中最好的头发.
Ben: Said you had the best head of hair he'd seen on a white man.
杰森:好了,很明显,我知道我在说什么.
Jason: Ok, so obviously I know what I am talking about.
嗨,亲爱的,
Hi honey, you are just in time.
你真准时.我在告诉本,我见过加里 帕克特.
I was telling Ben about the time I met Gary Pucket.
麦琪:哈.白人中最好的头发.
Maggie: Hu.Best head of hair on a white man.
本:爸爸,现在跟我走,我让你瞧瞧录音棚.
Ben: Dad, come with me right now and I'll show you the studio.
麦琪:嗨,我讨厌打断这个重要的会谈,
Maggie: Hey, I hate to interrupt this important pow-wow Ben,
本,但是你要把脏衣服拿到你的房间去.
but you were supposed to pick up the dirty clothes in your room.
本:爸爸.
Ben: Dad.
杰森:嗨,本.优秀的生意人从不做事拖拉.
Jason: Hey Ben.A good business man never pouts anything off.
本:知道,但是我这里完成之后,我们就去录音棚.
Ben: Ok, but when I'm done we go right to the studio.
杰森:行.
Jason: Alright.
麦琪:我真受感动.我从来没有见过他动作这么迅速.
Maggie: I am impressed.I've never seen him move so fast.
我想起来了,我从来没有见他动过.
Come to think of it, I've never seen him move at all.
杰森:我告诉你了,麦琪.他变了.
Jason: I told you Maggie.He's a changed kid.
麦琪:我们需要给迈克多少钱,
Maggie: How much money do you think we'd have to give mike to get him
如果我们想让他改变.
to shape up?
杰森:我们付不起.
Jason: We couldn't afford it.
麦琪:现在这提醒了我.你知道吗?
Maggie: Now that reminds me.We could you know.I was wrong before.
我之前错了.我去年挣了些钱.
I did make some money last year.
杰森:哦,不!
Jason: Oh no!
麦琪:你说"哦,不"是什么意思?
Maggie: What do you mean oh no?
杰森:麦琪,因为我们的税级保持在那,
Jason: Maggie, for our tax bracket to stay there,
我指望你的事业完全失败.
I was counting on your career being a total loss.
麦琪:但是对不起,我还有一点本事.
Maggie: Well excuse me for having a little bit of talent.
我去年挣了五千块钱.
I am so sorry I brought in five thousand dollars last year.
杰森:对不起.只是我今天对税方面比较古怪.
Jason: I'm sorry.I just get a little bit weird on tax day.
那五千块钱是非常有用的.
The five thousand is going to come in very handy.
麦琪:哦,不,我花了.我这里只有支票存根.
Maggie: Oh no, I spent that.I just have these check stubs here.
杰森:只是存根!
Jason: Just the stubs!
麦琪:是的,亲爱的.
Maggie: Yeah honey.And they didn't take out much with-holding.
他们没有扣很多税.我得到百分之九十九.
I took out ninety nine deductions.
我不喜欢百分之一那么多,
I didn't like this one that much,
但是这不贵,我知道你会高兴的.
but it wasn't expensive and I knew that would please you.
杰森:甜心,麦琪,
Jason: Sweetheart, Maggie, let me explain something to you.
让我给你解释解释.如果存在负现金流,就会有破产的危险.
There is negative cash flow and there is bankruptcy.
麦琪:下一件事情你也会喜欢.我们可以做广告.
Maggie: You'll love this next one.We'll be able to advertise it.
杰森:如果我幸运的话,某天她写出什么东西,获得那讨厌的普利策奖.
Jason: With my luck one day she'll write something which will win the stinking Pulitzer Prize.
麦琪:那是什么,亲爱的?
Maggie: What was that honey?
杰森:哦,没什么.只是在思考本变得这么有责任心.
Jason: Oh nothing.Just musing about how responsible Ben's been.
麦琪:我已经把他交给你了,小甜心,
Maggie: I've got to hand it to you sweetheart,
以前星期六前他从来不做家庭作业.
he's never done his homework on Saturday before.
杰森:是的,他甚至修了草坪.当然,
Jason: Yes, he even mowed the lawn.
因为下雪,看不见草,但是他的想法是好的.
Sure, you couldn't see the grass for the snow, but the thought was right.
麦琪:当在吃饭的时候他掉了一块猪排,他用自己的衬衫擦干净,
Maggie: And at dinner when he dropped that pork chop,
然后吃.
he wiped it off on his shirt before he ate it.
麦琪:是的,这另你惊讶,
Jason: Yeah, it makes you wonder doesn't it?
是吗?我应该多年前就把他当作我的合作伙伴.使得他容易控制.
I should have made him my partner years ago.Makes him easier to control.
麦琪:哦,因此这就是你为什么做这些?
Maggie: Oh, so that's why you are doing this?
杰森:不,但是它不是个坏的副产品.
Jason: No, but it's not a bad bi-product.
麦琪:杰森,你在开自己的玩笑.你用你的支票本来操控他.
Maggie: Jason, you are kidding yourself.You are manipulating him with your checkbook.
杰森:麦琪:行了.我没有操控任何人.
Jason: Maggie, come on.I do not manipulate anybody.
也没有利用我的支票本或其它东西.
Not with my check book or anything else.
麦琪:这样?你怎么想的?
Maggie: So?What do you think?
杰森:是不是贵了?
Jason: Is that the expensive one?
麦琪:绝对.
Maggie: Extremely.
杰森:这使得你看上去比较胖.
Jason: It makes you look fat.
麦琪:我把它给退了.哈,你差点得到我,操控先生.
Maggie: I'm taking it back.Ha, you almost got me Mr.Manipulator.
杰森:麦琪,我没有操控任何人.
Jason: Maggie, I am not manipulating anyone.
如果有,就现在让雷劈我.
If I am, may lightning strike me now.
杰森:本!
Jason: Ben!
本:恩,我在喝水.
Ben: Um, I'm getting a drink of water.
杰森:你溜进来的.
Jason: You are sneaking in.
本:如果是我溜进来的话,我会搞的像这么糟.
Ben: If I was sneaking in, would I make a mess like this?
杰森:刚才我认为你变得有责任心和成熟,本.
Jason: Just when I thought you were becoming responsible and mature Ben.
这就是我和你做生意的原因.
That's why I went into business with you.
麦琪:需要帮忙吗?
Maggie: Need any help?
杰森:不,我能自己处理.
Jason: No, I can handle this myself.
麦琪:如果你遇上什么困难,你的支票本在这.
Maggie: Well if you run into any trouble, here is your check book.
杰森:行了,本,怎么回事?
Jason: Alright Ben, what's going on?
本:我刚才把支票给劳拉 林恩看了.
Ben: I just went to show Laura Lynn my check.
杰森:停止,合作伙伴.合作关系跟这个没有关系,本.在这间房间里面,我们是父亲和儿子.
Jason: Hold it there partner.The partner ship has nothing to do with this moment Ben.In this room we are father and son.
本:那么我们去客厅吧.
Ben: Well then let's go out in the hall.
杰森:你溜进来干什么的?
Jason: What are you doing sneaking in?
本:我怎么进来?我溜出去.
Ben: How else could I get in?I snuck out.
本:我对你很失望,
Jason: I am so disappointed in you Ben.
本.
After I invested two thousand dollars in you.
在我向你投资了两千块之后.你会怎么想这对于我的感受?
How do you think that makes me feel?
我是说,
I mean is this the same boy who just hours ago stood in front of me
这是几个小时前站在我前面告诉我笑话的同一个孩子吗?
and told me a dirty joke?
本:嗨,我变成另外一个.
Ben: Hey, I got another one.Better.
很好.有个岛上全部是女人,而且他们只吃老玉米.
No there is this island full of women, and they only eat corn on the cob...
杰森:闭嘴.
Jason: Stop it right there.
本:你听过呀?
Ben: You heard it hu?
杰森:不,我从来没有听过,本.窗户的钱必须从两千块里扣除.
Jason: No I haven't heard it Ben.The cost of that window is coming out of the two thousand dollars.
本:但是那是用来做生意的.
Ben: But that is for business.
杰森:没关系.我告诉你不要提及生意.
Jason: Never mind.I told you not to bring up the business.
本:好吧,你是爸爸.那不公平,这钱从两千块钱里面出的话.钱属于我们的合伙的.
Ben: Well you are dad.That's not fair that the money should come out of the two thousand dollars.It belongs to our partnership.
杰森:哦,其中一个合作者应该考虑到,
Jason: Well one of the partners should have thought of that before behaving
在做出像个小孩子的事情.
like a teenager.
本:我是孩子.
Ben: I am a teenager.
杰森:我真的开始考虑整个合作关系是不是个大错误.
Jason: I'm really beginning to think that this whole partnership is a big mistake.
本:是呀,我也是.
Ben: Yeah, me too.
杰森:有个简单的方法去解决,本.合作关系终止.
Jason: Well there is an easy way to solve it Ben.The relationship's over.
本:你是说我不再是你的儿子?
Ben: You mean I am not your son anymore?
杰森:我是说我不在是你的合作伙伴,本.
Jason: I mean I am not your partner anymore Ben.
本:但是我们有计划.我有大计划.行了,这不公平.
Ben: But I had such plans for us.I had big plans.Come on, this is not fair.
迈克:啊,恩.现在是不是和爸爸说话的好时机?
Mike: Ah mum.Would this be a good time to have a word with dad?
麦琪:亲爱的,你忙吗?
Maggie: Honey, are you busy?
杰森:亲爱的,我忙的很.
Jason: Honey, I'm up to my eyeballs in this stuff.
麦琪:好吧,我去购物了.
Maggie: Ok, I'm going shopping.
杰森:不,不,不,麦琪.不,坐下,坐下.我有很多时间.
Jason: No, no, no Maggie.No sit, sit.I got plenty of time.
麦琪:我只想看看在我走之前你做的怎么样.
Maggie: I just wanted to see how you were doing before I left.
杰森:不,你没有,
Jason: No you didn't Maggie.
麦琪.你想继续昨晚的话题,
You wanted to follow up on last night and see if I had seen the error
瞧瞧看我在本的事情上我的方式是否错误.好了,麦琪,
of my ways regarding the Ben thing.
如果我的方法错了,我早就知道了.
Well Maggie, if I error in my ways I would have seen it.
麦琪:我不担心,
Maggie: Well don't worry Jason,
杰森.我不会提及那个事实,
I wont bring up the fact that it was a mistake to mix the father son
把父子关系和合作关系混淆.
relationship with the business relationship.
杰森:我没有混淆.
Jason: I did not mix.
杰森:真的?
Maggie: Really?
杰森:啊哈.
Jason: Uh hu.
麦琪:当你去找我们的会计,你是否先确定他的房间是否干净?
Maggie: When you go to our accountant, do you make sure his room is clean first?
杰森:事实上,我会这么做.
Jason: As a matter of fact I do.
麦琪:我相信.就像我说我不会提及那事.
Maggie: That I believe.Like I said I am not going to bring that up.
杰森:很好.
Jason: Good.
麦琪:很好.我想你会换律师的,如果他没有擦干净猪排的话.
Maggie: Good.And I suppose you'd change lawyers if he didn't wipe off his pork chop?
杰森:他不吃猪排.
Jason: Armed Swartz does not eat pork.
克莉丝:停下!蠢蛋,蠢瓜.
Chrissy: Stop!Crooked tie, crooked guy.
迈克:谢谢.行了,那好,我看起来怎么样?
Mike: Thanks.Alright, well, how do I look?
克莉丝:像个百万富翁.
Chrissy: Like million bucks.
迈克:那么,新转播价格应该很简单.
Mike: Right well then the price of a new transmission should be easy.
开萝尔:还有一件事,本.哦,不是本.
Carol: Just one more thing Ben.Oh, it's not Ben.It's Mike.
上,是迈克.看起来像本,穿的像本,从他小的高个的兄弟学来的.
Acting like Ben, dressed like Ben, learning from his younger, taller brother.
迈克:不要管我,开萝尔.
Mike: Leave me alone Carol.
开萝尔:我不高兴,迈克,我们只是关心,因为你穿了本的小西服.
Carol: Don't get excited Mike, we are just a little concerned because you are in Ben's weenie suit.
迈克:嗨,这不是本的小西服.这是我的小西服.
Mike: Hey, this is not Ben's weenie suit.This is my weenie suit.
麦琪:嗨,你没有穿着这睡觉吧?
Maggie: Hi, you didn't sleep in that did you?
迈克:为什么不?这不会皱.
Mike: Why not?It doesn't wrinkle.
麦琪:杰森,你的十一点钟的来了.
Maggie: Jason, your eleven o'clock is here.
迈克:爸爸,听着,
Mike: Dad, look if you got five minutes,
如果你有五分钟时间,
I want to tell you how you can make a lot of money with Mike Seavers
我就会告诉你,你怎么样和迈克 西维尔表演工作室合作挣大钱.
acting workshop.
杰森:出去!出去,出去,出去,出去!
Jason: Out!Out out out out!
迈克:我应该给他讲个笑话.
Mike: I should have told him a dirty joke.
杰森:哦,不,
Jason: Oh no, I can't owe that much.
我没有那么多钱.我从来没有见过那么多零,自从迈克上了高中以后.
I haven't seen that many zero's since Mike was in high school.
无论是谁,没有三万块钱就别进来.
Who ever it is, don't come in unless you've got thirty thousand dollars.
克莉丝:我有两块饼干.
Chrissy: I've got two cookies.
站森:两块饼干,行.
Jason: Two cookies, alright.
克莉丝:你为什么生气?
Chrissy: What are you so upset about?
杰森:哦,我说我需要两个失败的例子.
Jason: Well, let's just say I could do with a couple of write offs.
克莉丝:我认为,你说本和迈克是两个失败的例子.
Chrissy: I thought you said Ben and Mike were a couple of write offs?
杰森:是呀,不同类型.
Jason: Yeah, different kind.
克莉丝:有孩子真有趣.
Chrissy: It must be fun having kids.
杰森:有时候.
Jason: Sometimes.
克莉丝:我是说当他们倾心于什么的时候,就像我们的可爱单纯的本.
Chrissy: I mean when they fall for anything, like our sweet simple Ben.
杰森:嗨,本不是看起来那么单纯.
Jason: Hey, Ben's not as simple as he looks.
克莉丝:你在开玩笑吗,你和他相信你们是真正的合作伙伴.
Chrissy: Are you kidding, you had him believing you guys were really partners.
杰森:我们是真正的合作伙伴.
Jason: We were really partners.
克莉丝:当然.我喜欢你使得他信任你的方式,
Chrissy: Sure.I like the way you had him trust in you,
然后你把他当作臭虫碾碎.
and then you crushed him like a bug.
杰森:本,是你吗?
Jason: Ben, is that you?
本:是的,爸爸.
Ben: Yes dad.
杰森:嗨.
Jason: Hey.
本:是,我刚从与新鲜男孩见面回来.
Ben: Yeah, I just got back from meeting with The Fresh kids.
杰森:哦,今天呀?
Jason: Oh that was today hu?
本:他们在有线电视秀,我告诉你了.我只想让他们知道我们处在什么境地,还有我们的合作关系结束了,因为我打碎了窗户.
Ben: And they were on that cable show I told you about.I just wanted to let them know where we stand and that our partnership is over because I busted a window.
杰森:对呀,那么,啊,我想谈谈.男人对男人.
Jason: Yeah, well uh, I'd like to talk.Man to man.
本:和谁?
Ben: With who?
杰森:和你.本,
Jason: With you.Ben sit down.
坐下.让我跟你解释一下是比较困难,本,
This will be a little difficult for me to explain Ben,
但是我想试试.从一方面来看,恩,
but I'm going to give it a try.
本,我是你父亲.
See on the one hand, um, Ben, I'm your father.
本:迄今为止是这样.
Ben: I'm with you so far.
站森:是,但是从另一方面来看,瞧,我是你的合作伙伴.我曾经是你的合作伙伴.但是我没有把这两种关系分开,我应该分开的.这是个错误.你知道我在说什么吗?
Jason: Yeah, but on the other hand, se, I'm your partner.I was your partner.But I failed to separate the two relationships and I should have.That was a mistake.You know what I mean?
本:你在请求我的原谅.
Ben: You wish to beg for my forgiveness?
杰森:不,不全部,
Jason: No, no quite Ben.You broke the house rules.
本.你破坏了家里的规矩.那是你父亲,
That was your father who punished you.
惩罚你的那个.但是这不应该涉及到我们的合作关系.
But that shouldn't have interfered with our partnership.
因此,啊,我犯了个错误.
So, uh, I made a mistake.I'm sorry.
对不起.你愿意再次成为我的合作伙伴吗……
If you are willing to be my partner again...
本:你想再次成为我的合作伙伴?
Ben: You want to be my partner again?
杰森:是呀.
Jason: Yeah.
本:对不起,过去了.我不可能放弃新鲜小子,
Ben: Sorry, pass.I couldn't just give up on The Fresh kids cos you got weird,
只是因为你的古怪,因此我去寻找其他投资人,我已经找到一个.
so I went looking for other investors and I found one.
杰森:你找到了?
Jason: You did?
本:是.
Ben: Yeah.
杰森:那样太好了,本.那对你你好.谁出资?
Jason: Well that's great Ben.That's good for you.Who put up the money?
本:他就来了.在停车.
Ben: He's just coming in.He's parking the car.
迈克:爸爸,瞧瞧谁在这.
Mike: Dad, look who's here.
伯尼:嗨.
Bernie: Hey.
杰森:伯尼,你是合伙人?
Jason: Bernie, you're the partner?
伯尼:是呀.这孩子有做生意的头脑.一定从他母亲那里遗传的.
Bernie: Yeah.This kid has some head for business.Must have got it from his mother.
迈克:等等.你给了他两千块钱.好,伯尼,让我们瞧瞧枪.
Mike: Wait a second.You are giving him two thousand dollars.Alright Bennie, let's see the gun.
本:等你把剩下的听完再说.
Ben: Wait till you hear the rest.
伯尼:嗨,听着,我们在彩排的时候就与新鲜小子达成协议.
Bernie: Hey listen, we made our deal with The Fresh kids at rehearsal.
本:两小时侯他们会去录制电视秀.某个唱片公司的人看中他们了.
Ben: Two hours later they are taping the show.Some guy from a record company loves them.
伯尼:叭达兵 叭达蹦,他们花了五万块钱买了我们的合同.
Bernie: Balla bing balla boom, they buy our contact for fifty thousand dollars.
杰森:五万块!
Jason: Fifty thousand dollars!
伯尼:还有这些孩子跳赖跳去,制造噪音.
Bernie: And all these kids do is jump around and make noise.
本:我们平分利润.瞧,
Ben: We split the profits.
支付本 西维尔那部分,两万四千块.
See, pay to the order of Ben Seaver, twenty four thousand dollars.
伯尼:哦,顺便说句,当明年你缴税的时候,
Bernie: Oh by the way, when you do your taxes next year,
我不在是个会计.我是经理.
I'm no longer an accountant.I'm a manager.
我开豪华轿车,订房间服务,我还不是已婚男人.
I ride around in limos, order room service and I am not a married man.
迈克:两万四千块.
Mike: Twenty four thousand dollars.
杰森:好吧,我首先承认这点.
Jason: Well, I'll be the first to admit it.
我用钱来控制本是错误的.
I was wrong to use that money to control Ben.
麦琪:首先承认这个?
Maggie: The first to admit it?
杰森:还有其次.我错了,我是猪脑袋.你们高兴了?
Jason: And the top two.I was wrong, I was pig headed.Are you happy?
麦琪:非常.
Maggie: Very.
杰森:令我吃惊的是本对于新鲜小子的看法一直是正确的.我们不应该低估他的判断.
Jason: What amazes me is that Ben was right about The Fresh kids all along.We never should have underestimated his judgment.
麦琪:我们!
Maggie: We!
杰森:我.我.我我我我我.好了,
Jason: Me.Me.Me me me me me.Ok, I was wrong.
我错了.本发现了他们的才能,这才是才能.我不应该怀疑他.
Ben spotted their talent and that takes talent.
对不起,如果我怀疑过我的哪个孩子.克莉丝:爸爸,
I never should have doubted him.I'm sorry I ever doubted any of my children.
我需要动手术,医生只收现金.00:21:34,200
Chrissy: Dad, I need an operation and the surgeon only takes cash.